[
    {
        "question": "How much is 15×5?",
        "choice1": "65",
        "choice2": "70",
        "choice3": "75",
        "choice4": "80",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "How many minutes are there in 5 hours?",
        "choice1": "200",
        "choice2": "300",
        "choice3": "400",
        "choice4": "600",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "How much is 22 + 33 + 44 + 55?",
        "choice1": "100",
        "choice2": "144",
        "choice3": "154",
        "choice4": "164",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "How much is 9×8?",
        "choice1": "52",
        "choice2": "62",
        "choice3": "72",
        "choice4": "82",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Divide a square into two equal triangles.",
        "choice1": "Divide equal triangle",
        "choice2": "Divide square as triangle",
        "choice3": "half the square",
        "choice4": "Divide a square diagonally",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "How much is 555-55?",
        "choice1": "455",
        "choice2": "55",
        "choice3": "400",
        "choice4": "500",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Draw two lines on a square to create four small squares",
        "choice1": "draw equal line",
        "choice2": "draw line in side",
        "choice3": "draw lines in both side",
        "choice4": "draw lines through the middle of each side",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the next prime number after 5?",
        "choice1": "6",
        "choice2": "7",
        "choice3": "9",
        "choice4": "11",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": " What is -15 + 15?",
        "choice1": "30",
        "choice2": "20",
        "choice3": "0",
        "choice4": "3",
        "answer": 3
    },
    
    {
        "question": "How many centimeters are in 5 meters?",
        "choice1": "400 centimeters",
        "choice2": "500 centimeters",
        "choice3": "600 centimeters",
        "choice4": "300 centimeters",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": " How much is 22 + 33 + 44 + 55?",
        "choice1": "100",
        "choice2": "154",
        "choice3": "134",
        "choice4": "144",
        "answer": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "Where is more milk: 10 bottles of 0.5 liters or 5 bottles of 1 liter?",
        "choice1": "The amount of milk is the same",
        "choice2": "10 bottles of 0.5 liters",
        "choice3": "5 bottles of 1 liter",
        "choice4": "None of above",
        "answer": 1
    },


    {
        "question": "How many minutes are there in 2 hours?",
        "choice1": "60",
        "choice2": "90",
        "choice3": "100",
        "choice4": "120",
        "answer": 4
    },

    {
        "question": "A designer makes $25 an hour. How many hours does it take for a designer to make money on a $100 sneaker?",
        "choice1": "4 hours",
        "choice2": "6 hours",
        "choice3": "5 hours",
        "choice4": "3 hours",
        "answer": 1
    },


    {
        "question": "How many centimeters are there in 5 meters?",
        "choice1": "400 centimeters",
        "choice2": "500 centimeters",
        "choice3": "300 centimeters",
        "choice4": "600 centimeters",
        "answer": 2
    }
]